MATTHEW ELIOT

Phone Number: +65 8333-3833 Email: matthew.eliot@mail.com

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/mattheweliot

NRIC: S693696F

Summary

Senior Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Technical Skillsets

- 1.Python
- 2.Data Analysis
- 3. Project Management
- 4.Full Stack development
- 5.Complex problem solver
- 6.Devops

Certifications

PHP Framework (certificate): Zend, Codeigniter, Symfony.

Programming Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, PHP OOP, CSS, SQL, MySQL.

Experience

09/2015 - 08/2015	 Web developer Luna Web Design, New York 1. Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences. 2. Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow. 3. Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and 			
	optimize usability.			
01/2016- 03/2017	Graphic Web Designer Tether Development INC, LOS Angeles			
	 Design and develop Online brand creative pieces including landing pages, banners 			

Education

08/2013 - 08/2016	Bachelor of Science: Computer Information Systems		
	Columbia University, NY		
04/2010- 04/2013	Diploma in Web Design		
	Singapore Polytechnic		